her name in the temples of night golden wings glowed in the candlelight
crowds came running just to see the flame but envy was the price of fame and now he stands
where the echoes fall with tarot in hand hearing every call from praise to venom in the same breath
burns gold, not red
Oh, hold on, the lens cap was on.
Yeah.
Ah ha ha!
Sorry.
I was like, why can't I see shit?
Hi, ethereal, hi Jamie.
Hi, what's up ethereal?
Now I can, now I can put my.
It kind of works. I don't know. I'm trying my best right now.
Hey, what's up guys? Hi, it's Shan. Hey, what's up Shan?
You didn't see it. It's been a while. I know it's like so many people like are just starting to come back now after like, you know, it was just crazy for a while.
So, let's play a little cute song.
This one is about to be an introduction song for the channel.
See if you like it. I think it's pretty good actually.
Thank you again for the presents.
Thank you, Arizona.
Anyone, I can do a reading, too, if you come up
on the pre-reading.
I would prefer someone that wants a reading, come up.
Let me fix my screen.
How was your day, guys?
Oh, I pre-produced it.
Hi, Halo.
I got coffee left.
Oh, darling, coffee.
Oh, hi, hi Tricks.
Tricks over there, look at you, you made Tricks in there.
Hi, hi, what are you doing?
Hi.
Oh my God, first.
Hey, what's wrong?
Hi.
Hi, hello, Mr. Tricks.
Be happy, look, he's just purring, he's purring away.
Okay, I'm gonna go down there.
Tricks, are you a happy cat?
You're a happy cat?
Yep, you are.
where you want to sit right there
relax right there
my good dad
or my poor dad
do you like me or not?
do you like me?
yeah so
you know I feel kind of bad
you know
some friendships
I'm really happy to be seeing a lot of people that had left and stuff like that.
It's just, I'm sorry, but, you know, things got weird or things got bad or something happened.
I know a lot of people left because of, like, the different reasons and, like, I don't
necessarily have anything to do with people.
Yeah, so you're a little cute.
You're a happy guy.
You're a smile.
My tricks
Sam ended a show one day where I was like throwing tricks
I got the ball because I was picking him up like probably kind of couched me. I was like, I was like that.
I live in my arm. He's like very docile, you know.
It was kind of funny though. Hey, how are you?
Tricks is a little, he likes to be in the house all the time.
He likes to be in the house, like sit right on my lap and sleep with me under the blanket.
I don't know how long I'll be here tonight. I just wanted to come to you today, post the week.
I want to thank Alexandra Mayer, mayors. I was looking today. I saw her show was on. She was
oh, Q-ness overload. Yeah, but she was reviewing my Trollpedia. And so thank you so much,
Alex, for reviewing that. And, you know, I think she's right by half of it.
The review is on my community wall, you can see it there.
It's really your sweet review and peace so much.
Oh, you're just purring, aren't you?
You're just purring.
Do you hear him purr?
Oh, you're meowing out loud.
You're saying hi.
What are you meowing about?
Want to sit with me over here?
Can you give me a kiss?
You do, you do?
Oh, hi.
Close sir. Oh, oh don't show don't show everything except for the imagination. Oh my
Oh, you kiss this make me kiss this
One down
Yes, they're lucky cat cat
You just turn your friends allowed
Oh
Have a little grooming session, okay
They got first today
Huh, I really want to make some more like
Movies, I think that's kind of the hardest thing is being really cool animated things like the ones that I did
Really expensive and I'm trying to like figure out
still do cool like animated things but like I did I was on the right track with the little
unscorpial video which I did post on that regular videos if you want to like watch that video
um I animated that it turned out really really good oh here we go oh so we have here
oh it's me hi hi how are you oh my gosh it's like he I miss you so much I'm so
I'm like, I'm so proud of you all the time.
You are?
Oh.
You're watching what happened with Bita and stuff?
No, because, nah, you're so strong, dude.
You just like, see it.
Thank you.
I try to be, I mean, I've been through a lot of stuff,
and so I have a thick skin, but I'm holding the camera
to say hi to you.
Want to say hi to Chris and Marie?
Pull up.
B!
Oh, Lola, is that Lola?
It's Trixie.
Trixie, that's Lola's song.
Trixie, hey, baby.
Hey, Trixie! Trixie, I look crazy. Don't even look at me. Don't look at me. Trixie, don't look at me.
Oh, okay. Trixie, I just don't want to be odd with you.
I think Trixie might be a gay cat, I'm not sure, but I'm a little bit feminine.
Well, you know, I've been kind of emotional a little bit. Like, you know, like, you know, it's really a thing.
Are you okay?
Yeah
Well, you know, I'm saying it's like it's like really great for people to have like some backbones
huh
Yeah, I mean, it's like it's about time. I grew one, you know, so that's been like just putting up with like a lot of like
Bad stuff that I shouldn't have been putting up with but I've been like I'm kind of like
I, um, I, today I felt so good, you know, it's like such a different vibe, you know,
when I like get away from these people, like I'm doing great things and I just, I eat that,
that I like waste so much time.
I did feel like a difference, like it's like, you know, it's like people started coming
back that had not been here for a while and they're like, yeah, I kind of got, felt like
Some of them felt like it had a taste away some of them just didn't like how the show was going
Which way I should do my hair. I I don't know what I clipped it somewhere
The bottom. Oh, sorry. Sorry, buddy
You're absolutely fine. Oh, I like it. Hey, what are you doing?
So, yeah, where do you so where have you been? What do you have to anything interesting? Oh my gosh?
I've been so busy and you know what so good, you know, what's so good is that not only have I been busy is that
it been at
Better for you and me and us the better. Yeah, it has been better
No, we're all gonna hurt. We're all gonna make you tether better. That's what I'm saying. Yeah
You guys better I think we're I think it's like a healing process and it's like there's people that want to heal together
And there's people that want to like continue to hurt people and like trying to get in a network of
helpers of
supporters and
Like kind heart of people looking for anybody's support. I am
No, listen, I got like all the love of my life, you know, honestly
Not that I do but you know what I mean
Yeah, but it's good to have like people around you that aren't aren't like fucking with your head. They're not like
Sneak dissing you they're not like abusing you and stuff and then it's and they're just like and they're they're healing too
And it's like you can like be accountable with each other
So I know they're gonna talk about my ceiling that I had a tornado storm
I don't even know. I just I got a new tornado. I haven't got my
roof replaced, you know since it almost
new way for Sharon Watson saying hi do you know Sharon Watson yeah like Sharon
she's in chat saying hi yeah Sharon's cool
hi Sharon nice to see you here I don't think I've seen her here Sharon's the best
Sharon could be okay I want to know what Sharon is doing
Sharon, what are you doing? It's Sharon ever come up on panels?
Sharon come on up. This is a link up or if you want to come up. She's at LOL. I don't know if she wants to
Sorry, see I'm moving around because I move around to everyone's like why are you always rocking?
He was like he's just sitting there rocking back and forth
Well, you can't see what they do to me when I'm still, you know, they put my eye and they put my like body and like
They put like me every other way than myself
Right. So what does it mean? Like what does it matter?
Well, it matters that you know yourself and that you're confident you love yourself because it's like, you know a lot of
Even if everyone in the world is against you, you know, you still have yourself that can be your advocate try to
try to like you're right no I'm saying as far as they're fucking back bullshit
you know why would I even fucking acknowledge some of these backhand
bullshit anymore and like how can I do it and do it yeah I know I'm gonna stop
stop I'm gonna stop mentioning names and stuff about it because and they're just
like saying oh he's obsessed with me I'm not obsessed with them just like still
Got a lot of unresolved things and it's like of course I'll never get the closure
So we have to figure out how do we fucking talk about like shit without talking about
Motherfuckers about them thinking motherfuckers
Well, we get we can do it in private. We can we can do it, you know, or we can use code names
You know
We can just like, you know, use other people's names or something. I don't know. We can tell our story to that
I wish I could tell you like I had like such a great day
I wish you could see where I like come from and like
the like because it's so great
Yeah, yeah, and you know, it's so even more beautiful we're like
Like, for instance, I don't want to go into too much detail, but you know, like, people
own a lot of money because they owned a prize, like, I guess you can say, object, as far
as, like, you know, location, location, location.
You know what I mean?
Well, yeah, it's real it's one of those things that never goes down in value really always goes up
Yeah, and one of my mine
I'm not gonna go into that but
the one rich and the whole I think
Okay, never mind
like in the area and like the and they net we never sold so we never sold so we
have so much in it and every bit is like almost like so much money they want
every they're like oh my gosh I will give you everything for like just like
very little amount of property yeah so you're gonna sell their property for like
a lot of money that's what I'm saying that's not selling oh it's trading or
what no it's never trading and that's why my grandma's house is in the middle of
that area and there's all these fucking you know what I mean I was like and then
They want millions. They want millions. They've already like there's over a hundred million for that property, but
Wow, it's not going. Okay
Well hundreds of millions, you know, you can buy some like bigger property somewhere else. I mean it's like
No, it's the fact that it can go up. Hey, guess what we have? We have somebody here. Hold on
We have somebody else coming in his name is high. Hold on. I mean, I need to go and be on it one second
Oh my god. You guys think he smoke a cigarette? I don't want you guys to see me smoke a cigarette.
Okay, you're hitting.
Hello?
Calm down.
Yeah?
It's me dude.
Hi, I'm Jill.
Hi, Rando.
What's up?
You're on with Crystal Maria and the psyche.
Oh my gosh, please don't.
What?
It's Rando.
Don't porn bomb.
He's not gonna porn bomb, he's Rando. I know who he is.
Okay, hi.
Well, he's a great guy. Look at how good-looking he is.
It's a mask.
That's a mask.
Should we wash again?
No, I'm gonna...
I have, like, another face cream.
Huh?
I got this one.
Like, I bought these, like, things where I never even used it.
Like, why haven't I never used it?
So like here you are combing the cat. Yes one grooming grooming the cat
You have a nice meat pussy
So I
I hopped in I was watching like crystal Marie was going on and you're like you're like kind of like ignore me
You're like what the fuck is she talking about I could sense it
Maria Crystal, what are you talking about?
Yeah, but it's just confused me
No, I was talking about products
Yeah, I
Was talking about items when you sell when you're like younger like you know like
You mean like what are you talking with the fuck is he talking about bro? That's what I'm saying
So I guess why hopped on like what are you talking about lady? You're like, uh, yeah, exactly. That's what I'm saying. Oh
Shit, no
I'm the only one I was the only one up there. Oh, I'm here. I'm right here
Oh
No, but listen, but listen
She doesn't have to hide. She doesn't have to hide
No, I'm good. I'm good. Dude. I was just saying like
You know those
Like back in the day
Yeah, I don't know what the fuck
I've been back in a day back in the day when I was young
Yeah, you own the whole fucking you own house you buy house like for a hundred and fifty thousand you buy the whole fucking town pretty much
You didn't find out until you find you find out
Well, can you translate rando or anybody in the anybody in the chat? Well, I don't know what I mean
She's she means well, but I kind of came on to help out like I didn't want her to
I'm just trying to be nice
Like I bought like areas like I want to like really picks up and then like come to find out
You know, it's like I bought a whole town for like
Fuckin $5,000 you bought it whole town for 5,000 the town did you buy it?
Okay, I don't think she is so you okay, do you need crystal can you that I'm an ambulance?
I
Just I just feel like we can do it for you one day and you could do it so great do what?
Yeah, right do what?
We can buy all that for like 15,000
Like a ghost town or like, you know, yeah, or like in America. Yeah. Yeah, right here
Like you fucking 25 miles away from fucking
Sanctionary
Right from where? Stictionary? Yeah, why do they have to be next to a sanctuary?
This place is crazier and crazier every time I hop on something just crazy
I know yes
Where do you live the Vatican
I mean, it's like
Okay, you're not making it like I can't even understand what you're saying though
Nevada is it heaven backwards
Nevada is a town in Kansas that is awful but it's right back to a sanctuary where it's a trail rain
Where you can meet that trail rain all over the country if people really want to be very weird about it
That trail range leads everybody.
You could go everywhere in the United States
by that train rail, even if you took it off rail.
But you have to take it off rail.
Sike.
Yeah.
You've got to admit it, dude.
If this was your family member, would you
want her doing this?
Would you want her up here doing this?
I think that's why they have this thing called 50-150.
Like you wouldn't want your like sister or your aunt or whatever up here like crystal. You'd be like, yeah, just
Yeah, you'd like to get off line, you know what I mean? Like
What are you talking about? I know but I'm like pussy like fucking peanut shoes are pussy to every dude and dude that was
Is he online extreme never do shit like that. She's like she needs a 51 50
Yeah, that's more of like an embarrassing thing because you're kind of not making sense. I don't know if you're under the influence
Uh, I think you're just having people laugh at you. I'm just trying to help you to know
how that happened.
I don't know if that's great or bad, but you think it's, uh, because people can embarrass
you more?
Crystal.
We're gonna take a trip down memory lane. Do you know what your memory lane is?
Uh-huh. Okay, we're gonna take a trip down memory lane. Do you want to go? Let's go. We're gonna walk down.
This is what happened six months ago. I
I met Crystal Marie on my show
Yes, sir
Hey, so we started from the bottom, now we're here, girl.
I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm so sorry sir. I'm
Oh, yeah.
There's my mark right here.
Oh, I live.
Oh, I miss.
I wish I could just like love your whole life you know yeah you're so not nice though I know how
Ever son. Oh man. I know you don't like me. You know, that's okay. I do like you. I like you. I love you
You mean, I don't like you. I've always been nice to you
Oh
You're funny you're you know a little bit a little bit
Unpredictable
Thank you, you know who I am actually
I don't know who I am, actually.
It's kind of funny that, you know, it is what it is.
I'm a mind reader, and you are not a good, even more than Aaron Carter.
You don't think goodly.
You actually are not pretty nice to a lot of people.
Hey, you know what? I don't give a fuck of what you could because you don't even know who I am
So therefore you are getting me mixed up for somebody else
Where you don't even know who I am you're fucking wrong on everything in life. You're dead on everything on life
You have no fucking control on everything
You have no control and everything in life and you have no life
I'm telling you
I'm telling you you are
You do not know like yeah, I feel bad about that one and I wish I could tell you more about
But I would never tell anybody more than they could handle
Oh, sorry
Lucky you were so great. I was. Well, thank you, but I thought it was kind of funny. I thought we were being funny. I thought it was being funny.
You were. I thought it was hilarious. I thought it was hilarious.
People don't even think, I mean, I don't know where their humor goes to.
See, because their humor goes dark places, and I go humorous, so when their humor goes dark,
I go darker.
Well, yeah, but that's kind of like, if there's dark humor and you go darker, that's kind
of scary.
Like, I'm like, hi, Crystal, how are you?
And you're like, you don't know anything.
Yeah, haha, hi. I wouldn't like that though. Not like that. Not like that.
It's okay. It's okay. That was kind of, that was kind of scary a little bit. I was like,
what did I do? Are you stupid? You don't feel like that anymore about me or you just, you're just kidding?
No, that was some, that was the music in the background. I told you they were playing it.
Oh, the, just the Golden Girls theme. That's what, that's what I heard.
No, that that other guy was playing it. I know
Okay, okay. Thank you for being a friend
No
There was this guy that was playing this fucking
Got a devil music in the background
The tannic music was yeah, who was he? Was it me?
I don't know, was it you, was it your friend?
Rando, do you play satanic music?
I heard you playing a guitar before.
I didn't play the music in the clip.
No, that was a crystal, that was a cult of clip.
It's when people edit, you know, you
and they attach other audio stuff to it, like audio files.
And so it's called a clip.
That's from the 80s.
You know what I mean?
You ever see that show crystal?
Yeah.
Dude, I'm telling you, there is something going on.
Okay, that's not you explain to me. I thought so too, but I
You were kind of interrupting your own clip with your own voice it was like that's what was it really going on
When he was playing it you were talking you're like interrupting yourself
No, she just did.
I guess for this, I guess for this, I guess for this, I guess for this, I guess for this,
I have to go you know that I don't feel like the same way about like you you're a real fucking man
Just care just careful with the word because I don't want any at the AGOTS are watching
Okay, I'm but why will be I'm so sorry though
You know, you know, but it really makes me upset that these guys are really not
No, I'm talking about how great of a man you are, like, all around in, um, baggads, like...
Dude, I don't know. The drag queen the drag King's like the women that dress like men
Did you ever get fooled by one of those crystal? I
Have no
Vagina
Good question
You're like unzipped a zipper and like it was Levi's and there was like a sock falls out and it's just
Well, it's never I got like a very small pussy. Oh my god, okay crystal that wasn't that's fine. That's fine
Okay, tell us more about it
Do the carpets match the drapes?
Is it like a wild bush or is it like a nice shape?
Okay, never mind. I didn't say anything.
You know, do you have Brazilian wax down there?
Or just Lady Venus?
There's a lot.
Hello?
Hi.
Okay, I've heard it from his question
Yes, I ran you talk to her for a second you came here. Oh fuck
Hi, it's okay
So yeah, I just came on to try to help you out. You were kind of not making
Okay, um, we will debate. Um, what do you want to do buddy? I'm not a ghost
I'm not a ghost. I don't do the debate thing.
That's him.
No, oh, no, Aldi's gonna try to banger
Oh, he's gonna try to hit it
You don't like Aldi like that
Did he try a crystal did he try
You know that you kind of notice stay away
Well, yeah, yeah, he's a sexually abuser and stay away from him everybody. Oh
Good to know I don't want to get sexually abused by LD I
Kind of do I'll see how he you want to
You're down for whatever man
You know, it's really fucking weird. I always
Yeah, what are you saying you went like down a tunnel and
Is
LD's sister and him, you know, they do porno
Together together. Yeah. Thank you. So I get together
Yeah
You cannot say that without any leg
Yeah, you can't do the bestiality stuff he's monetized channel crystal
There's all video
My doggy Dylan Bobby Dylan doggy Dylan
Well, you want us to Google that on fucking I mean, they don't even put that on porn sites, dude
Run run run
They don't even that kind of shit on prawn sites crystal
Hi, how do you want us to Google something like that? Like what the fuck you talking so you don't watch dog?
Yes illegal. Yeah, I
Never seen it
Yeah, you just did
I
Scrub your fucking hard drive chris if you actually watched the LD doon that stuff scrub it
Oh boy, they didn't have the fucking online 10 years ago like what are you talking about this?
No, it's not your line
I mean the guy's probably a creep, but I don't think he's got videos online of him fucking with animals. Come on chill
No, I'm talking about Bobby Dillon. You know that chick?
The singer? Bob Dylan?
No, uh, Justin.
I'm the, I'm the changing.
Justin fucks dogs on...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, please don't accuse people of that.
He's in the chat, dude.
Yeah, Eldie's in the chat. Eldie, can you please come defend yourself, please?
Eldie was her manager.
Why would he do that to his sister?
Eldie was her manager when she fucked the dog.
That doesn't make any sense
Like why would he just like you're like a normal job like instead of like, you know, like
Nish
Doesn't make any sense because
Well, you should her mom was her manager her main manager
Her mom and her dad
Okay, we have some we have some confirmation
Explain LD. Come on. I'll come on. I need somebody up here. I can understand
I'm hearing very strange things
No, I know it's very strange. I can't tell you I don't want to even I don't really want to bring it up too much
Okay, well, I mean it's too late. I mean the dog's out of the bag now
So, yeah, I
Just told you everything I knew like
You hey listen Chris. Do you know hold on? There's accusations here. Do you get high like what drugs do you use?
Are you are you high drunk? What do you what are you on right now? I?
Would never do a drug. I'm scared of a drug. So you're drunk. Are you drunk? How many white clothes? I?
Haven't done any white clothes when they done about
What four shots, but you know, it's like I just don't drink
Very often honestly, I drink once a week and it's like I drink a lot
This is the night that you drank and this is why this behavior you're having
But it's not wrong
Well, yeah, I mean if you get drunk in your in your room all alone, I guess, but when you like put it online like this, it's
Kind of not good
No, I'm saying that you guys are doing shit that
You guys want to portray me as a different than I am
You're the one portraying
We were just talking about normal stuff, like
I could summary that's kind of true. Yeah
This ain't a debate either. This is no debate. I didn't say that
I was just reading the chat dude. So you have literally reading the chat
My chat died my chat phone died dude my chat phone died. I don't
Chat phone died. Yeah, this is normal. There's just another night at my show actually
So anyway
What else is new
No, I never said that that's a fucked up dude, um, who said that I gotta see what she I gotta see what they're saying
My gosh, so you're saying that I said that
Where we have it off we have everything on video, so we'll be able to just play back
Right
So play it right back
Can't you play it right back just say anything
Not really smooth kind of slow. How many viewers you got?
29 yeah, I don't think that you're being honest with
Probably left some heat watchers and stuff like people that are just in shock and unable to type right now
I wouldn't say that bombs
I know but we had some bombs dropped today
Okay, which one oh the one she just dropped. Yeah
Yeah
Well, somebody was confirming it kind of I think this
Erin are you talking about like which what are you talking about Sharon said she saw the video. Yeah. Yeah
Sharon saw the video of what Sharon will these yeah
Of hooves LDS or him prawn video in a dog involved I guess is what you said. Oh
I
Think she forgets what she even said so I could sit sits. It's over. Yeah, I do she forgets what she said
You didn't say anything memorable at all
Yeah, I know I didn't nor did you that's why they didn't remember anything that you said they just remember in me
Oh
Delusions of grandeur
She's delusional. I like my picture
That's me
Where'd you go?
You Buddha, or did you like change?
She ran away the dog changed layoffs. No, I didn't she just ran she let's you go
I
Like my thing crashed and then when I came back in she's gone her phone probably died, huh?
Maybe or else she's just didn't want to be alone
I don't know. I want to be alone with you. Oh, no
What was that about
Geez rando
Play my
Because we have a full moon tent, I'll play my Aquarius moon, so here you go, enjoy.
Okay, how are we doing guys? I don't know. What are we going to do tonight?
Remember we used to like have like 10 hour streams and stuff and now I just want to like
run the TikTok and stuff.
I still have some burger left.
Yeah, well, I mean I got readings if anyone wants to come up for reading. I got you Crystal. I'm sorry
I didn't mean to like chase you off.
Brando, I'm sorry I'm gonna choose you off. We got 40 people in the chat. Nice number.
can go over some stuff, whatever you guys want to do, whatever you guys want to do.
But yeah, and if you guys would like, okay, I have a link tree set up, and I really like
link tree.
I really like it, because I can do a lot of stuff with it, and basically like all you
need is a landing page really, but it makes it easier to integrate some stuff into it
So anyway, I have a really good link, nature, that is my website now, I have my book available
there, I have a booking place there, I'm going to be making an online course and I'm
offering, also consulting or offering a few things, I'm offering, I'm going to be restocking
my Etsy store with a bunch of stuff, like new readings and things like that, there's
Price levels. I think I'm gonna try to do like a five dollar reading or something like that too like just
You know, I need to I really need to
Get my you know, I just after all this slander and
Negativity and like all this crap talked about me and people are like, oh my gosh
So I really need I want to I really do want to prove myself that I'm very talented reader
And so I'll do pre readings tonight and I'll do
I'll have some inexpensive options on the on Etsy. You can go to metaseki.etsy.com
all the links are on sekiawakens.com. I think you'll like that website. You can also
buy the trollopedia for five bucks. You can actually watch the review if
you'd like to. It's a short review and I really want to thank Alex Mayers for taking
Let's keep it positive. Yeah, we're keeping it positive
Yeah, somebody come up. Why am I why am I funny dude at rando? Oh, yeah, I made that joke
God who's the adult and Israel with Peter North? Yeah, Peter North's probably the first male porn star I saw
You were a small role in David's videos. You were acts were you a male or female?
You saw the video. Oh my gosh
math delusion
I don't know, so yeah, I talked to Danger Ranger today and he was actually really friendly
and things like that.
And he liked, you know, I don't like the allegations, you know, I hurt myself, but I really would
like to have him come here and talk about, maybe the audience can ask him about something.
Oh, you're a male?
Okay.
Can you send me the video, please?
But yeah, of course, you know, I really cannot like me how to animal, so I'm really
I need to hear his side of the story, but I can't see a video about where he's explaining like he's just sick
You know, he's just had to take the dog to the vet for something, but you know, it sounds like I
Don't know if you're a different thing, but here's a nice guy to me on the chat. He was sick
Very helpful. So
How are we doing? We got 41 people
Well, I know I'm making I can show you like some old clip of the show or something, but
I just don't know. Yeah, we can go to memory lane. I think that was fun with Crystal, like where she's watching this and that, but we find an old episode.
Um, live video...
I think it's liked.
See my channel.
And...
Five.
Oldest.
See if we got anything.
Razzie, where are these people?
I'll be up on the show, oh, here.
So this is the oil party, joker and pie.
I look kinda healthy here.
SIG, joker, oh, here's a joker.
Can I take off camera or can you do that? Uh-oh, where'd you go? I
Don't know she disappeared
Crystal
Well, anyway show my screen here where you go, oh here she
Hello
Crystal you okay? Yeah, I'm fine
No, I just look crazy.
You don't look crazy.
You look beautiful.
Ah!
I look crazy.
I mean, look at me.
I'm like, I look terrible.
You look beautiful.
What are you talking about?
Jeez, Louise.
Oh, there she is.
No, I think, um...
Rob, I am with this.
Okay, hold on.
The thing keeps messing.
Ah!
It goes back to me.
Big, tall, sexy boy.
Why so big?
I don't know about Joker, man, with that mustache.
That's not normal. You don't have a fucking brown mustache and black hair
I'm hitting Riverside. I'll be downtown Riverside pull up. Oh my god, BG. Now that I have you up here
BG what the fuck is up with the angiomime a bottle
Hey guys, I'm not slow and so it's like
Right person, hold on
Does anyone know why he has a bottle of fucking syrup next to him every night?
I just wanted to ask BG why did he get his ass whirled by Mike?
Who the fuck are you and uh, okay, he came to the pool.
BG where'd you go buddy? I want to ask you some questions real quick bro.
What's up with the whole situation with Mike man?
Come on BG. You got it. He's got you man. Yeah, you gotta have some kind of excuse, bro
Some kind of excuse
Come on
Crystal oh sorry sorry
You're fine, you're beautiful. Hi. Hey, how are you?
Oh, no, I don't want my face on here, dude.
You're really happy?
Here, I'll put my face on.
Look, I look worse now.
Now you're the most beautiful woman in the world, never.
Right?
You got me.
I look terrible.
Look at my hair.
Oh, my hair.
There.
When we make a cute couple crystal,
I look like Jeffrey Dahmer.
You look like that, you know, Lorena and Bobbit.
And, you know.
No, you're beautiful.
You are beautiful.
Oh, I have a really great stomach.
Yeah, I do too, look at mine.
Can you see mine?
I don't know if I want to show mine.
How does that look?
It's good.
Great.
Thank you.
Okay, someone said take off your...
Yeah, you can show yours.
Well, I don't know
Okay, do you have a hole in your jeans?
It looks like there's a little hole in your jeans.
Okay, that looks like mine.
Really twins. Hold on, I'll put myself back on.
Guys, let's compare.
Good. No, I'm fat. I'm fat. I'm a bloated dude. I just ate six cookies. I feel fat too. I think I'm
a minority. I just had a McDonald's Big Mac. Oh, dude. My mom, I made cookies and then my mom,
like my mom was like, yeah, because like anyways, but she made good cookies.
She made brownies and I made cookies to bring her
You what kind of cookies you make a chocolate chip you want to see him I
Like I love a Pillsbury like the dough and then you like like cut it up and they're not that great
I mean, I do have like this little cutter. Oh, oh cookie cutter
Yeah
I want to get a fun shape, like a wiener shape, if you're funny.
So they're really normal.
Yeah, they're normal.
They're all boring circles.
But that's cool. They look neat though.
I'm so sorry.
You're fine. Did you cook tonight?
Did you hear Chris K is going to want to come over and masturbate with me?
Not just be
I don't know. I don't like that. I shouldn't do that. He said he had $100,000 in cash. He wants to come over
Well, I would say don't do that because he used one of the ones that was
What's the Bernice say gang that had like a lot of money to murder me?
Okay, let's not
Yeah, he came over there night and he's like hey like money talks. He's like how does everyone want to see the second
I do a chatter, but then he said he says a lot of things and he acts a lot weird
Yeah, I
Know just be very
I was told that he might just try to beat me up, but then I watch the video
I'll be very weird do be very weird. I watch him fighting with a black dwarf and the black dwarf kicked his butt
So I'm not even scared anymore
I'm not kidding. You see that the door
He found a door in Las Vegas and he lost
Well, I seen something else where he tried to act like he was a cop. Yeah
Yeah
I'm sorry, I mean interrupt. Yeah
No, that guy that that
Entire life
It hurts my entire like inside. Yeah, I don't like him picking on a homeless guy
He went to the guy's tent and he was like yelling get out of the cops and the guy like took his phone and like
He started like pleading for his phone back
When he did that that meant
He's worthy of death. Oh my oh well, it's like I think he's just ignorant maybe you know, it's like yeah, but that's pretty ignorant
pretty ignorant
But I mean, we're all we're all gonna you know pass away something. I mean, it's like we're all human beings, but no we're all
we're all um
I'm saying he he deserves it
Well
Hopefully maybe he can change his ways. That'd be good. You live in cheap people changing their ways. I
Don't you don't okay, so
I do, but I don't, I don't think people will change.
He didn't hurt the guy, I mean, he just like,
kind of like, harassed.
But for him, he would never change his ways.
Well, thankfully he's the most biggest in the California,
so I probably don't have to worry.
I'm saying for, there is that way,
there is that direction, there is that feeling,
That love and that gesture that that you want somebody. Oh my gosh, this person is gonna be fucking better
We're gonna fucking make sure this motherfucker. Oh
My god, is there any way we can help this guy or fucking put this
You know what I'm saying
Who you trying to help which guy anybody
Any single soul
Chris can a game that stalks you
Well, he was in the white that whites courtesy game that did hurt me that was trying to kill me
You know, aren't you without you're like a part of spanish or something?
They don't like spanish. That's kind of weird. Oh
No, I wasn't in he was in a game that is against me
Why were they against you though? Oh?
They were trying to kill me
They did with Jar Jar stinks is backing you up, and they're all saying yes. They did
Why would they want to do that? I don't do they want to kill me. Do you think or unalive me?
Well at that time
People were saying that I was married to a black guy, which I was never married engage anything to a black guy
We're married to Sam
I would love to be married to this black- oh my gosh, look how bad I look.
You're beautiful.
I should put makeup on.
You look fine.
Just put on a filter.
Put on a filter on the camera.
I will put on makeup for you.
No, I'm not doing that.
We'll do that though put on lipstick and I was watching a Lisa Jordana recently and she like she had like this male assistant
And I was like looking at him and he had a full face of makeup like he has like lipstick and it's like
I don't like to sit there and like I like to be like Al Bundy with my hands off
And I like to add button. Um, like just like just like this, you know
Put your hand down in your
in your um, nether regions
Be careful Chris. I don't want to get in trouble
No
No, but what I'm saying is that these people are being very mean. Oh my gosh
I look terrible. See this is why I don't want to be on there
You're an avatar on the team. I can cover you
Come out if I make you look like this
How do we do it? There's you right there
Again
just be the voice of these people right there. I'll be the monster, you'll be the object.
All right, Crystal, how are you doing?
I'll be the monster, you'll be the voice.
How about you be this one?
Oh, that's me, that's actually me, Greg.
Crystal can be this one.
Crystal, someone says you look fine.
Don't you tell us that you're not too spongey
because you're willing to give every part of your heart.
Hey, Crystal, do you want to see...
In all of the willings, nobody knows that.
I know I'm the best Disney princess.
Come
Face anybody
And I will want to
And I will say to you, you won't have to worry about me.
You might have to worry about your family from their family trees.
That's what I said. You might have to worry
When you say shit about me, you might have to worry about
Three
It's still yeah, you get the job and uh, you can be in our movie
I will be the queen of the sheets.
I will be the queen of the ugly, the queen of the sheets.
I will be the queen of the ugly.
Only, this is the only place you can hear this live.
Because my ugly wins money, and I'll blow everything that you will see.
Anybody? Anybody help? I need some little help here. Hello? Anybody?
You'll learn you see a soul that you don't know
And you let it control by the trolls
You're as ugly as they are and you know you are
Just know that you're ugly
Me?
You're ugly as can be.
You're not very nice, Crystal. I mean, it's like, I hadn't told me.
Just know that you're ugly.
Uh, hold on a second. You got this?
Natural in disgusting you where you could be.
Crystal. Crystal.
You hear me? Listen to this.
Hear you clear
Should I hear you clearly again?
Right there, are you gonna listen to me try?
I know you might not listen to me try
Do you mind listening to me try?
That's about the only time you can
But it's right
You're not gonna explain me any more
I guess we're done in here, flowers are done
They're flowers, they're fucking dying, they can go fuck too fast.
Crystal. Oh, hi. Hi sweetheart. You're back home.
Just wanted to let you know some people are like really mean and that's gonna be okay.
And you know like that first thing I told you these people like that the fucking I told you like that the same people or
Like you wouldn't even believe that their age, you know what I mean? It's like
over a hundred years old
Well, I'm saying that that I wouldn't understand that a bitch
That would act like that like that is like I guess she she's like a lot of criminal record
And she's trying to cover it up. So
We're just gonna break it
Christine that we not that Christine. We all know. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. She's got a big criminal record. She's about to get fucked
Aaron your cat friends
No, no, no. Yep
Why what you do she was a criminal?
Yeah, she's a bad criminal
But she do
She kills kids. Oh my god, please. Oh, no, no, no, no, no
You're gonna go she kills goats
Well, he puts them in, they put them in these sex trafficking rings, and her brother and
her friend probably fucking are part of it, and we're gonna get them all fucking caught
real quick.
Yeah, they're not trying to help people, they're trying to get people fucking caught up.
That's sick.
Christine does this?
Yeah
Why do you think that she says that she's a part that she works for
fucking listen
she says
that she is
What's it called, you know first aid what do you want?
and
She also says that that she's
She's
First-line security
Yeah, she said she's a security guard at the mall on the weekends, right?
No
No, she said that or is that what she told you
Yeah, she works with Alex at the mall
Well security
Maybe I can fix something else, so
Do you ever do security lady, but yeah, so she's she's falsely sick security so she can
Do other bad things with other parts of law. So yeah, she's fucked
Hopefully hopefully like you know, no, she's going to jail forever
I wouldn't really mind going to Jefferever if it was me because I'd finally get like a city supply of sex
three showers
Yeah, but you're not a bad guy and you would like excel because you're like a man
But I don't I don't think I see that I get trouble though. I think she's like
Think it away with it
I'm sorry that you think other things but um
I can't tell you anything, but you know those people that use the system, you know, that
say that they're doing, like, companies and, like, and they say that they're getting this
people houses and they don't, and they got, like, they're giving a difference in so
Uh, yeah, you know, this is all fucking false and that fucking bitch is about to go down and she's about to have no job
Yeah, they're all doing bad, you know, it's it's about it's an all system
It's a bad system that's about to go down from Georgia to uh, there to florida
What are they gonna do?
They're about to get him to go to prison
That's gonna happen soon or this year. What do you think?
I don't know how that works
Who's gonna go first Epstein or?
Christine
100% I wish Christine was here
Well, because she did bad stuff online and it's it's caught up to her
Because you can't pay people you can't people people to abuse you people it's against the law
Yeah, that's wrong. This is consensual, right? And that's I say I want you. Yeah, so and when it's on video and it's yeah
It's against a lot when it's been by five people
Yeah, and on different networks, we are not even the same fucking people so who is but so who has a video of pristine I think
It does not all the same
Well, we couldn't out because it's it's her work. It's what she did
It's her it's out of her her her own
Device Christina, I really hope that out of her own device. You know what you mean device, you know
No, when people do bad things under their own device
Yes
So, you hacked Christine. Well, that's illegal too.
No, no, no, I never, I would never, no, she fucking hacked, tried to do bad things to me.
Okay. Christine, I need you, I need you here.
Years ago, years ago, I got this years ago.
How long ago?
She doesn't even know. I got all her shit years ago.
How many years I told you this I told you this I tried to tell you this
This is why I did not want the fucking
Fagotry I said when when I seen the thing with
The
Then I knew the gods inside you don't even know what I knew
Is our God
Well, no, they have like they
You know they're friends with people that aren't friends with us
You know like criminals
Yeah
Yeah, well, that's why they have like a Rico stuff, right?
Not the eviction to his criminal games
Well, I'm telling you I don't know what to do. I mean, I didn't know what to do at the time
I know what to do now, but I
Know we're gonna do about this. That's kind of a good tire
This is Lenny, what do we need to help? Just do not be in trouble
But just ignore her I
Want to save her
Hey summer, she's a problem. She's a problem, dude. She's
She's a problem, dude, I got her I got her dude. I you want me to show you
Just be careful with the accusations because it's like a very serious activation
Basically the worst thing you're gonna accuse somebody of is
So I really hope that's not true.
Do you think that she's capable of that? Crystal? I don't think so. What do you think?
Crystal.
Crystal?
Have you lost her guys?
Crystal.
I can't see her up there. Crystal can't see.
Wow, guys. Well, yeah, there's no, I think she's getting the evidence together. I mean, it's like, I really, it's a very serious allegation.
I think we just have to say this is like, open a little, oh, there she goes. I think this has been a little bit of, it was just, that was just a play.
That was just like, we're just pretending. I'm sure that's not the end of that was true, right?
It can't be true. It just can't.
Anyone want to say hi? Oh
Hello
Big pipes
Hi, thanks. Hey. Hey now. Hey, how are you? What's up?
How's my my favorite paper paper?
Um, I got some vodka here. I'm gonna take a shot or two
Drink with me. Are you drinking tonight?
Um, I can get a white phone.
Yeah, go ahead.
I'll take a share.
I'm going to grab it.
Grab it, grab it.
Yeah, it's right out.
Right out.
Oh, I can do that.
I can get there.
It's okay. I'm just...
What's going on today?
Good night, good night.
I'm going to put my headphones on.
switch
battery one hundred percent like that
so
i got a hundred percent battery on my headphones
for someone that has
no use of a bright camera if you want to sound better
it's really sound terrible
I mean, this is going to be ridiculous.
Damien, I don't think anybody will use what she said. I mean, I think that was the...
She's talking about Christina. She's talking about Christina in the horror movie with the car. That's, that's, that's his name after that movie.
You got to give me feedback on here.
Yeah, you have feedback terribly.
Well, like...
Is this one better?
Yeah, she sounds fine. I want to see her face, though.
Alright, so this one's the communications one. I should be using I don't like it pointing at me
I'm going to point over there
What do you want to do? Does that one sound shitty?
It sounds fine. This one sounds fine. Absolutely fine. I just switched it to something
So pipes, what's up? Uh, not much. I was gonna take a shot of vodka here in the chill, but
Do it
You see it. Do I look good tonight? Do I look like I kind of look like an anime character, right?
How do I look?
Happy?
Do the shot, dude. Smiling.
Oh, sorry.
Yeah, it's a make-out, buddy
I'm not quite there yet, okay one more beer and this stuff does taste like
Tastes like cough syrup or something
You know what you can actually drink cough syrup and get kind of like a buzz off of it. I wouldn't recommend it
Yeah, I feel like I've never like abused it. I sort of have I used to like around COVID especially
Like I would drink like half a bottle to go to bed
Yeah, it's called Robo Dose and then like I would drink a bottle of Robo Tesla
Robotripin yeah, and I walk around like a robot actually and then I would like watch the shining and hallucinate
And then I would wake up the next day forgot what happened
I've heard people call it rubies before rubies
Because it's all red, there's a little ruby, like a little red...
Oh, yeah, maybe from the visual or something, but it's for the DXM.
Yeah, DXM.
There's a bunch of, like, Discord weirdos that are in that stuff.
Yeah. Well, I try to stay away from Discord as much as I can.
There's all kinds of bad stuff happening there.
I wouldn't know.
You wouldn't know? Aren't you on there?
I'm in like a banjo discord.
OK, so he's on discord.
OK.
Well, that's fine.
You're not on my discord.
No, I didn't even know you had a discord.
I do.
It's probably so many weirdos in there.
I'm chilling on that, actually.
Excuse me?
What did you just say?
I said there's probably a bunch of weirdos in there, so.
There's no weirdos.
There's me, and then, you know.
most of the grease gang and
But no weirdest
The grease gang
Ruby Jimmy black RG R bandolet. Oh
God those people are terrible to me. I know they're they're a game
Yeah, I wouldn't want to like I would never be friends with those people
Why not with the probably we have we have nothing in common really right because they're all in a game together and then
You know, so we can see the outsiders, but you know what mr. Big guys gonna start a game with me
Not really well, that's not
I start one it'll be like it'll be like a friend will be like a nice game
It'll be like more like the West Side Story game or really
Off the sick around key that did it. We just be like singing and dancing the whole time
You can buy with your instruments in your hand anyway. You're holding your guitar with your banjo or your
Monica
Yeah, the grease gang left
Anyway, okay, well, I'm not kidding good
so
well
Guys, what are we gonna do? Who else come up? Anyone want to talk to Pipes? Mr. Big Pipes is here
Special occasion Saturday night with Pipes
No
57 people watching I know it's exciting
Pipes pipes we report give the audience of 60. Can you do something exciting please? I'm dying here
This one's called, uh...
Okay, sing a song.
That's called Cripple Creek.
I don't even really know.
my banjo. I think I gotta play less banjo in more harmonica because my harmonica
actually sounds really freaking good, but it's like I want to shred banjo because
it's so much cooler kind of. I don't know, harmonica is pretty cool too. It's sexier.
Oh, that's the cheers. That's like three shots dude
Like everyone plays guitar
Alright, so you're gonna play?
Yeah, let's grab my guitar.
Ah, this picture of you on the screen?
He's got a pan flute?
Yeah, is that you?
If I had a pan flute maybe.
Oh I found you, I found you.
Maybe not, nevermind.
I mean I mostly just play harmonica, a stringed instrument.
I'm kind of limited to two and mr. Big Pipe says it's true about you. Hold on a second. Just look at this
Look at the screen one second
It's true
Van Dyke collection
Dick Van Dyke oh
Okay, I was like when I saw him is like I've a large dick and then I'm like
Yeah, I don't know who Dick Van Dyke is.
We need some black guys who he probably does.
I know black guys.
Hmm, it's going bald though. I might need to shave his head.
Yeah, that was a guy from Clueless. Wasn't he from Clueless? He was on Clueless or something, right?
Might as well be myself. Yeah.
Murray Poppins jokes, and I have a chim chimini chim chim. Can you play chim chimini mr. Big Pipes?
Chim chim churu
Let me psyche
Don't tell me you're running a fucking transvestite panel, bro
Who is you everywhere up here is a tranny me? I'm not ready. You're not you're not a tranny
But fucking the crystal marisa tranny big pipes in a tranny
Flurry diamonds a tranny
Reggie Dean is a tranny. There's like 30 people up here that are trannies or trying to hide it
So what I'm coming to the conclusion is that you're running a transvestite panel and
Bro, let me find out if I find out that you've been playing us for a fool like a joking because you know, you know exactly
What's a dick in a pussy?
Don't let me find out bro. You've been playing us for a fool for content and clicks and views
Because then that will be the end of you
Trust me, bro. Do not play me for a fucking fool. Is
crystal Marie a man or not?
I don't think so. I saw it. Yeah. Oh, I don't think so. You take head, you know, for 10 years. That's a man
Christopher is a man
You've been playing us for a fool for a year
Chris the crystal Marie. That's a fucking man, bro. That's a trainee. I don't know. Okay. I do know
That's the point
And I know you do too, but you don't give a fuck cuz you milk it for clicks and views
You'll let us dive into the depths of hell. You you knew fucking flurry diamond was a tranny
You didn't tell nobody nobody you let us dive into hell there. So listen to me motherfucker
You even let fucking some guy fall in love with him or make up Gonzalez. Hey kid. You don't care
You know everybody up is a tranny fucking mr. Big Pipe's is a tranny
I don't think he is he is
No, I mean it's crystal Marie is a fucking trainee. I'm sick. Yo, if I see another trainee up here, my man
It's this shit. Goodbye, bro
And not because I don't like trainees because I don't like playing for a fool
You understand all it was do like me go Gonzales
remember when you play me go Gonzales and let him fall in love with
Flurry diamond and laughed about it. Ha ha ha you knew that was a tranny
You didn't tell him you went along with it and laughed about it for clicks and views you got content
Yes, you did my friend and then you're still doing it with these people
Come on, bro. I haven't heard a tarot or cat thing in months. It's hero today. Did you? Yeah
What tarot?
You haven't done shit
And so and once again remember this you're at 2.6 2k and that's where you're gonna stay until I say otherwise
Your shit is frozen my boy. You're not growing no more. You were 2.6 3 4k 5k and now it got back down
2.6 2k and
There's nothing you can do no shorts. Nobody no trainings. You can bring up
When I say this panel moves it'll keep growing and that's what
Well, bye Alex
I
Think I'd kick you off
My number
Singing
I'm sorry. He's too loud. I mean it's like like to be Alex. I mean I let him I let him for a long like
Oh, who's back, okay.
Oh.
What a fucking asshole that guy is, huh?
He just comes up here talking all that shit
about your stream.
What kind of fucking asshole does shit like that?
Look at this guy, hold on, look at this guy.
What a piece of shit.
What a cute guy here, hold on.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't know we were fighting. I brought my ukulele. I didn't play something dude
Yeah, okay. I don't know. I'm on my shitty headphones. So I'm gonna take it. I'm gonna just play. All right. Yeah, cool
Somewhere over the rainbow way up
I know I'm thinking of you in a lullaby
You're going to have to change your audio for us to hear it.
Oh, sorry, hold on guys.
Well, it's like...
They're working on it.
The echo cancellation maybe?
I'll fix it. I'll fix it. I'll fix it. There we go. Try it now.
Got it. With the song. It's a Chrono Trigger song.
Well, like, with the accompaniment. Chrono Trigger is a game? The game with, like, the
Japanese game? Yeah, it's called 600 AD if the song is called 600 AD. The game is called
Chrono Trigger. Yeah, I've heard of that game.
Yes, sorry if you couldn't hear well. I have a decent Mike stream yards. It's a stream yard's fault
It's dream. I have a decent Mike for my laptop study this
He can turn echo it he can turn echo cancellation off if he has headphones on yeah, it's just me you won't be able to hear him otherwise
Yeah, Crystal Marie sir, what's your name, sir?
nah I just a few times a few months ago I look around just for random lives that
on YouTube and I've seen your lives and I used to run live so I'll answer your
question clearly because that was the where you come from and everyone goes
oh I don't know I just float around and stuff
I come from, I used to do lives, if you go to my channel, I commented in the chat, not
Cosmic Cam.
I haven't streamed in like two years, but I was in like the Opie and Anthony Howard Stern
universe, like those guys that like that kind of comedy and stuff, so that's kind of where
I come from, the part of YouTube that I come from, just to be clear and honest.
And I just found you guys looking up random live streams, that's it.
I've had Shulie on the show, I've had Wendy on the show, and um...
You've had Wendy? I, Wendy loves me, she knows, like she gets super excited.
I've had Hansie on the show. Hansie is super fun to talk to, but he's super paranoid.
He thinks everyone's out to troll him. I don't know if it's like a mental illness thing or what.
Yeah, he was like that when he was on the show too. He'd be like...
Yeah, super skittish.
Yeah, that's oh my god, you'd be like paying these people you didn't pay me like you get all that you're gonna
You're buying these people are like conspiracy
Yeah, super into conspiracy stuff
Yeah, you're a pretty talented guy
Like where about to you from?
I'm from Dallas, Texas
Crystal you're in Texas crystal
No, I'm just born in Corpus. Okay, she's born in Corpus. It's nice. Like Selena, Kintanilla. I like it.
Yeah, she's actually related to Selena.
She's lying. That's what every girl from Corpus says. Don't believe that.
Didn't do that.
Dude, like she literally told me that.
I'm sorry, I feel like I interrupted something. I feel like y'all are like fighting
I just I got like half a beer to finish. Can I just hang out? I'll just watch
I'm trying to be nice to people
Your name is um, I'm being nice to these people
Cosmic
I'm trying to be ridiculous. Okay, because
Good for me
So, you know what I'm crystal. I'm trying to chill dude. I'm always trying to chill
dude
Pikes, you know where we stand, you know what? I don't I don't know. I've never talked to the real crystal
Marie
I've known you for like five years or some shit four years, and I've never talked to the real crystal, right?
You've talked to the like I'm real dude. I don't know if you think I'm pretending or some shit
I've got Chris and Marianne. Mr. Big Pikes. Have you ever hooked up?
Absolutely not. No, I like
And no comment
That was a hookup with you think considering
Like like 10 streamers hookup. Okay
Yeah
Wasn't I would discord is for isn't discord for hooking up
I feel like I boiled it down for that.
Are you jerking and hooking up?
I have no stuff to go to one place.
We're going to go to, we're planning to try, but see,
this is the thing, is that these people were making it real.
Some people were making it real serious,
and some people weren't.
So we were going to say Chicago, as far as the Midwest area,
And there's like so many people
There out of been like and then you guys like to say oh my god. She was just like what there are to be like
Dude so the cosmic D. Are you are you a straight guy or?
That's a girl. Yeah, I'm a straight guy. I'm not a girl. I'm a guy
I'll be
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And a penis.
two out of three of the
three out of three of the
I don't know why you guys want me to be racist.
I don't want you to, I want you to be loving an old woman.
If you're racist, go for it, I'm not gonna support that.
You don't even know my, I'm like a 50 fucking, a 5500.
Do you know that I am like...
I'm Spanish, German, fucking Moroccan, uh, like, you don't even know what I am, like...
She's a United Nations.
Exactly.
I saw your body earlier that you're fucking...
Crystal, are you related to Pocahontas, Crystal?
Ew.
Holy shit.
Can we die now?
No.
Not yet.
I'm not I'm not I'm not dying until I can make it until no
That guy like every time he says that it makes you want to die more. Oh
Me yeah, yeah, I saw it so your butter
Why'd you like it's a compliment
uh
I saw this guy he was posting nudes of you and so what so what so you can
Jim next
No, it was in Jim next channel
Aye aye aye
You know the court system is like jumpy or something
The court system I feel like they don't take any of this internet stuff seriously
The revenge point is serious. That's something the court system definitely takes seriously as a revenge warning to people.
I know that.
But no, she was showing her body on stream like 30 minutes ago.
Oh, no.
But also, this was the nude set. He said that you sent him to him, and then he was posting them on Janick's stream.
Definitely never did.
His name is like jumpy.
Every new he was like sending me death threats and stuff
Is it public record anytime pistol gets naked is it usually just public record just to get you know
Okay
Crystal have you ever been naked on camera never she said she never has
I
Good times shared your needs to
Damn it. You didn't see what the name like that
When you're in the shower like as soon as it happened he like like mass message like like 20 different people
Yeah, that's fine because you're all going to prison
Because it's all recorded and you're all going to prison because I was underage at that time actually
Oh my god 17
What? How old is Crystal?
This is the time for the wires to be shared.
Crystal is like 20 years old.
Crystal, why are you so excessively naked to people?
I met Crystal by the way
What are you saying?
Why do so many people
Well, go ahead
Cosmic
I just asked her why do so many people
have her nude
She's fucking hot
In the relevant
I'm saying
When I was
Okay
What these are on YouTube? Yeah, they only have one picture and I was 17
So hold on just cuz I've been on YouTube and I've been around streaming for a while
So yeah, so do you sometimes like to hang out and get drunk?
Maybe dance around on streams and stuff like that
That's not a mine
So say so you like everybody looking at you and stuff like that, right? No, I do not I
Have to fight because what am I gonna do?
I have like a wheel like of life, right?
Where yeah motherfuckers keep bullying me and pressuring me and and fucking with my entire life
They fuck with my jobs. They fuck with my entire lives. What do I do?
Well, that's not doing that. I'm not like involved with those people
What do we do?
Yeah, teasing and making fun of someone is one thing someone going after a job
You know
So guess what I do I work with the government now
Oh, no. Oh, no. I feel like she's she's mega. I don't know why she liked me. I got an FBI on my fucking self.
Thanks for Pam Bondi.
Oh my god, Saggy. Some people have to protect themselves. What if I do too? Wouldn't that be funny?
I feel like Crystal's Pam Bondi is like number two, you know what I'm saying?
I think Rissa has like she can like kill a man with her like
Bear hands. Well, you know what? You know what I did today and I never the black mold in her kitchen
This can't you know a can
What's your deal with I
Was sitting there and I was very upset. Oh my mom is her mom's name
and I've been oh
We'll never mind, but I was there and I was I was
winning this can
In my mom's arm, you know really hurts me that my mom's arm is upset because we all have the same arm
That hurts ourselves, you know, we are
My mom and I are like the same
like, we have the same hand that we oh we get the same age your mom or the same age
it doesn't make sense no they have the same hand i believe it what she said so that makes
perfect sense right i'm jealous of crystals teeth person i think i'm sorry i mean interrupts
first i'm sorry no my mom and i have the same hand we're we're both uh we have the same hand
On my mom. Oh, okay. You're built like your mama. Just say that. Yeah. Yeah. I'm just like my mom, dude
But when my mom gets hurt, I feel like I get her everything that happens like when I like something like twins
100% but 100 years apart. Well seven or
100 years down though. Mom's catchy space for no reason. Yeah, she's almost as old as Christine. Hi
I
Know mom's is always the gold standard. No my mom's
In the fifties in the fifties
But she's really cool pictures
Known pictures. So does my my deal
So does my all my family members and like they're old like like they're all fucking
gallery like like all gallery like as far as like looking like back in the day
when those like what do you call it like old school like in that picture I like
our parents are telling me the last supper
Right and they're and they're in Vegas right in like a Vegas area style, right?
And there's like so many people on it's like so classy. I'm just
saying
I'm just saying that our family members are areas by Matt
Because my family members are not the way that
Beedah's Beedah's families are the helpers
That's why she keeps saying that
Beedah's family my helpers
My dad probably
Dad and mom
Is crystal okay, I thought this is like a normal person at first
Crystal
But you drink a fit of fucking vodka, I guess, but you don't know what I did to you.
Do you sleep?
Like, what the fuck?
And then I came home and I went to the, and I went, but I had a really great night.
Good.
Yeah.
Hey, I want to talk to the new guest.
Okay, so this is, so Cosmic, okay, so.
I'm thinking of No Crystal, sorry, go ahead.
Okay, I'll shut up.
I think you're interesting. Oh, I'll leave. I'll just watch. Oh, come on. I don't like that. Don't leave me here with Crystal. Oh, no. No, I got a bit off more than that. All right. Well, it's okay. My name's Cosmic. I'm from Dallas. Okay, see now we got something on me.
Ask him.
Crystal, are you okay? Crystal. Crystal, do you remember Hurricane Katrina?
Crystal?
Ask him. Crystal. Crystal. Of who? Do you remember Hurricane Katrina? Oh, of course. And do you
remember the they used to have those FEMA trailers they these white trailers that
they brought out and people lived in them for a while and what happened is they
started being sold and auctioned off.
They started getting sold and auctioned off to people and the problem with these trailers was they weren't meant for long term living
They weren't even a manufacturer for that purpose is so they would get filled up with like black mold
That would end up people would end up sick with asthma and psychological diseases
Just because they were living in these FEMA trailers way like 20 10 years later
You know and they're just like subjecting themselves to this mold and this bacteria that were in these
You know what I'm saying, Kristen? Yeah, everything. Oh my god. Yeah, it's crazy, right? Yeah
It's just something, you know
Oh, just so you're not sick of it. I guess
Oh, it's a good talking to you. Um talking about something different
Well, I mean we could talk about your nudes, but I mean I feel like I don't have any nudes
You do
Of where
Like when I was under age
No, like you did this on YouTube, dude
What did you do crystal you didn't
Remember good time said he had cancer and he his death wish was to see you naked and then you took a shower and the camera fell
Yeah, yeah
Can't show on your own time
It's not you really don't know anything and that's really disrespectful to you
To save that
Well, just like it like it's not because you know why you say it's kind of funny. I think it's kind of funny
Okay, okay
You see how it's gonna work out so don't forget how it's working out hey hey blackout
He's not here blackout black pipes back big pipes
Black pipes cuz you remember good times with JJ. He would go down
Mr.. Big I'm dumb
You're done
You're done your parents your whole fucking life is you're done. Oh
Come on. This is like she starts to threaten me to kill me and stuff. It's dark
So crystal the from what I'm just gathering as like a officer. I'm like I'm like a pre-office
It's just arriving on the scene. You know what he does sir. What did he do?
He wants to go ahead will come in right me and threaten me
Crystal what it's no I don't me down and yes
That's what pipes does
You don't even know what things I've been like
I've been
Gangs at one time. This is why we're gonna have to kill a lot of people at one time. We'll see we say stuff like that
Minecraft obviously in Minecraft we're gonna have to like Minecraft like
like
This guy and all of his stupid fucking stupid fake bikes and is all his fake chargers and his fake knives
What community do you come from crystal?
It doesn't really matter doesn't okay fair enough. Yeah, I mean why not true
Yeah, I can tell
Where's he come from? Can you?
Can you my first interaction do you want to tell about yourself?
With as you want to tell about his own great charges. You know
Yeah, do y'all know Molly go lightly I met and Carter through Molly go lightly keep going sorry
So it was like Aaron Carter stuff and then but the first time I saw her was in this. He's so wrong easy
discord
in like 2021 he's so stupid called crack and cold
this is the dumbness of it all
so what did you do to ericard?
what was your discord call?
ericarder wanted to talk to me
i never talked to ericarder one time
okay that's why fucking grafstra is so obsessive with me
because ericarder wanted to talk to me every day
and i never talked to him nor did i ever fucking
was I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was nice and I was
No, I wasn't you know the that guy was trying to set me up
This guy these guys were trying to send me us up. This guy said things and
You know some people fall for it and some people don't
Well, I think you're trying to like
No, shut the fuck you're trying to my life. I didn't let you know. I don't like you
I don't like you and I don't like your what you're about, dude
Well, what am I about? No, you're about bad, dude. You're about fucking crystal. Where were you when Aaron Carter passed away in that?
I'll tell me I see that. Oh
My gosh, poor and crystal. I never knew where in comment
Killed him trash we killed him trash. It was the one was supposed to meet up with them that weekend. Who is that? Who?
Trisha, yeah
Were you ever on tan soda with her and she said she had all these bad things to kill him with
Hey, I can't believe it and she had this news. Yeah, and she has a news that she is
for uh for for uh for girls for your girl uh now she's a news just for your girl
which girl
yeah it's like a death cult of these weirdos yeah
well what what do you mean
hold on but who who who what girl are you talking about crystals
lisa like they want to
These explain I'm dying of suspicions. What? Oh
I should like Christopher
Are you kidding me? Everybody knows it, but huge fan of crystal
but
Everybody knows that
Fucking
Alexandria was a huge fucking shit sturdier
She's stirred so much shit. She like made shit stirred that wasn't even fucking stirred
She should open the fucking soup shop with so much shit. She was tearing up. I get it
Crystal please don't damn out Alexandra. I love Alex don't don't get wrong Alex was like so bad for me though
because Alex was my friend and then she just like gave she just like
I defended her for like everything right and then she became like she was like mad and like by the way she's she like
If she's got videos of fucking justin fucking a dog
It's not crystal I feel like that's just a mental in the speaking. It's not even just that though justin's mom
Do you know justin's mom?
No, well everybody has a mother I assume
Well, her mom used to be in this shit big time and so she fucked like all the guys and
And and do you know all the characters she's talking about I
Know she's mom is more into the fucking madness
Who are you talking about with me?
Would just
Like I can validate right now. I'm saying that Alex Alex did all this stuff, right?
With just in and shit and her mom and then I rolled and her brother's her brother
And then Alex guess what Alex did she left me and then he made himself
Sister your poor name
Whatever go fuck yourself
No, like so LD his name is little Dylan and
Bobby Dylan her poor name
Her name is Bobby Dylan. He was a moderate Bobby. Don't he was trying to chase your point you not know know what you don't know about this
fact
Tree is that he was her porn manager
He was the one that was that's what I'm saying. He was on set porn manager. Yeah, that's that's insane Dylan
Yeah, and
Yeah, these people are what's a sicko family
Okay
That's why I had so much problem with he comes on here to like manipulate woman and then the brother was like already the fucking
The manager he was trying to manage. He didn't know what the fuck he was doing
But the father was in the calm criminal activity. He's a criminal. The father is a direct
Criminal he is a mob person
You know
And just you know how to get fake body parts to make themselves look
Liable as a woman
There was that there was that video it kind of went semi-viral and it was like two years ago
And it was just this random
Interrogation video drug guy and he's rambling on in Florida about ditty and like doing all this fucked up stuff for ditty and like two
Years ago at the time it was like oh here's a crazy drug guy talking about ditty
And then now in hindsight like so many years later everyone's realizing that interview going like
holy shit. Now that guy knew
exactly what he was talking
about. He this guy wasn't just
a crazy drunk guy. This was a
guy was probably got fucked by
Diddy. And I feel like Crystal
might be that like she's
holding some information. I
just don't know what's wrong
with her. I don't know if
she's on medication or she
needs to be medicated. Like I
don't know which are the
problems she's having.
But I feel like I can't get out. I'm struggling to keep up with it. I'm sorry keep going rest. I'm just not telling all the info because I don't want to give all my
Shit up and when the fucking beat
You know, like I'm like I'm a long soldier. Oh, we're probably
In this moment
want my shit like people to know what I know like later you're gonna find it
actual like everything that I've said they always say oh look at Crystal she's
crazy and then it's factual okay so this is just another thing that's gonna
happen crystal the chat is telling me that John Sarah quill which is like
And I consider like the prison or the jail drug.
I never done a drug.
OK, sorry.
It was serious.
Just randoms in the chat, just writing rumors.
I get it.
I know how it goes.
What is saraclua?
Yeah, who knows?
Yeah, right?
Who even knows?
I mean, is that like, is that like, vitamin?
It's a lot of vitamin.
They just add such like, vitamin.
It's like the generic
Anxiety calm you down drug that I know like people in jail and prison get
That's why it's carry up just curious
You did this girl when I was in high school this girl in Spanish class. She used to just give me several bills
I didn't like it. It's not a good high. Sorry. Go ahead. Crystal. I always interrupt you. I'm sorry. Go ahead
You're saying no, I would be to be quite honest with you. I never
have been
You know, I went I wanted
People to look at me as like psychology like psychology wise and I'm a fucking
I'm fine. I'm brilliant
Contravagantly
I wish I was a dumber, but we are getting there with you guys.
We got to dumb ourselves down, we got to make ourselves not know about things, and just,
you know, we're doing it better.
that
Um, I don't like to rush. I like to be on time
I never like to rush and I like to be on time. That's the main thing that about it
And I'm not gonna pull anybody's time
Like I'm not gonna waste people's time. I'm always gonna be on time
So what
Nothing. Just yeah, I'm just curious. Sorry
Feel like I got you I knocked you off track
No, actually, I like to get up early in the morning. You know what I like to do. I
Fix every bird like, you know like we got birds. We got crazy squirrels and
You're a bird lady
I'm all the ladies. I'm all the ladies
I live close to a
It's not lady or bird lady. Sometimes they conflict.
I'm gonna take a nicotine here.
Yeah, if I can, I'll feed the monkey.
You know, we got a monkey that...
Oh, outlets.
Oh, press on.
Let's just speed past that, Chris.
I don't even know what you mean by that.
Um...
Oh, I think Chris will sort of...
Well, I don't know what you're doing.
I never had monkey break in your car.
Have I ever had what?
A monkey break in your car.
No, never.
Well, you don't know shit about Kansas City.
I don't I don't like where this conversation is going because I don't know what you thought. I don't really well
You think I have fucking fucking zoo animal is gonna fucking hurt or fucking scare a bitch
No, first time. Yeah, no, you're wrong. Yeah, no first time
Yeah, I would hope that the edible troll would cut it but that zoo animal word safe. Yeah, guess what?
When like a person like myself you can shoot them on property
Crystal you have a burger in your nose
That you have a burger first like kind of like Texas. I have to trim my nose hairs
You have a burger
Shut it's all right
I hate that guy. Don't listen to anything fucking pipes, Big Poop says.
Poopy! Poopy! Poopy!
This crystal dude, the tarot card reads, the millions he'd be good at it.
No, they'd be terrible. They'd be kind of funny though.
You should let her just take it over one night and let her answer to people.
You think anything poopy would do tower. It's like breaks or something
You think your mom is gonna let you drive
Dude, alright, so one of the first things that she would always say to me is that her biker boyfriend is gonna stab me
My biker boyfriend, by the way, I have a biker boyfriend
Do you have a boyfriend? Who's your boyfriend crystal? Can we meet the old chap?
There's some guy that like walks behind her camera sometimes she says it like that. So do you have a pamphleting with you?
Well, he wouldn't be a
Motorcycle he would be like more like an athlete as far as like a fucking football player
You fucking faggot figure it's a fuckout
You should shut the fuck up. Oh, I'm she don't
Whoa
Chris to look at the camera look at it. Oh, nothing
Something tells me she's having fun
Saucy tonight
Chris something tells me
Like why don't you just be nice like when you're like, that's what I'm saying. She's pretending like it's so weird
Something tells me this is a very charming girl
Turn the camera off. I'm tired of looking at you guys.
I don't have no fucking makeup on.
These people are gonna be angry as fuck with me.
I'm good with this.
I'm trying to be nice to you.
Yeah, go fuck yourself.
Crystal, I guess we'll all turn my camera off.
I think you look better in real life than the profile picture.
That doesn't even look like you.
Yeah, Chris. What is this?
Yeah, I have no makeup on right now.
And I just cleaned. I just fucking weeded in the fucking whatever.
I'm sorry, Chris. You don't look like Santa.
I weeded my mom's yard, which I had to go like hours away. It's fine.
My mom, her arm, which is so crazy.
Hold on crystal crystal. I'm sorry guys. I'm done with my drink. I'm gonna go lay down
Thank you for letting me come on your panel though. I'll be
Thanks for letting me out brother. Hey, thank you. Have a good night. Thank you for being here. Yes, sir
I'll stop by again if that's okay. Yes, I'll buy
Okay, that person is either that was he was a his name is cosmic
He's pretty cute. He's he'll be back. Oh, you know who that is. I don't know who it is, but I just met him
That's um probably
that guy that was
Beat his ex fiance that was like was being nice and then he wasn't and then he said he was discussing and then he said
You know
You know claim to be another person
Yeah as at the sweet pink people in chat, I can't like leave
Eric from Cotto, I think
We actually got like that information more than she thinks that because she tried to threaten us
But she's run me
She's run me the week prior for like three weeks. Oh, so I actually have everything
Prior that she had brought me live
And we were going deep as far as getting her back,
as far as, you know, making sure she falls on her face.
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
Okay.
I mean, if you're gonna rant about something,
at least tell us what you're talking about.
Yeah, because you're not making any sense at all.
I mean, it's like, you could like,
just make a little bit of sense
that you kind of appreciate it.
Do you want me to make more sense of this? Yeah
Like so I can understand tonight. I'm like an idiot. I don't know anything
Well
The thing is is that that guy
There is a
Lover of men right that are we working under Peter's
That guy and you know and listen and see my guy that girl and she's only making $25
Listen and same with that other girl and then listen. Why do would they even matter as making $25?
You think hurting somebody's heart would be worth?
like $5 and like at $25 bows
You know what I mean?
would not I would not do that I just do it on my pure evil heart if they're doing
it to me but but listen it's quite a few people working together I can I just
don't know how to articulate it
I mean, why are you mean to me exactly? I could tell you exactly. Okay. Okay. I'll tell you where the problem started and how for me
How about for me?
Okay, yeah, they go for it. Okay, when the problem I
Was friends with good times and then
Good times I've told me and not very much time to live
right and
I would stay on the phone with them all the time like literally 24 hours a day
Non-stop all day at work
So inappropriate
Almost lost my job, but guess what he done
It took a video or he found or he
See this is where the thing because I never even knew and so when those videos were coming out
I was like, oh, it's not right. I
Didn't do that, you know, we you know, there was no sexual thing going on so
You know, there's nothing going on. You know what I mean? There would be nothing for me. So I was like, oh, that's not true
and
Yeah
This is like a story of how you've been you started getting harassed by people and stuff online, right?
Go on. I'm curious.
And, uh...
I kind of became more mis...
Uh...
They were trying to give me to be, like, a little bit more...
Know myself, and like...
Uh...
They were like, well, it's already out, and I was like, no, it's not, but...
Everybody was showing all these videos and like I never got no videos
But they were recording me and my when I was taking a shower and when I was like
Talking to my mom
They were literally recording me in like taking those videos and putting them on on the internet
And acting as that was like a sexual video or like
Yeah, you should expose those people
Well, I need to expose all of them
That would be you included what did I do?
Because when you exploit
But somebody's videos when you have no or
Things like those pictures. There was a picture of me when I was 17. They said they got it
You can go extreme and that's like the news I saw you and then like shit that good times posted on his channel when I was 17 18
And they got that that guy and like I'm crazy so me bringing that up is is me saying like no these people are shitty
They do that to you
Letting you know
So I'm having your back. I'm just saying yeah, I never said that they weren't and I never said that you weren't
Because I always said that you were a fucking piece
Big piece
Why do I do you lie you try to tell people that I like wanted to meet up with you. That's a fucking complete lie
Yeah, excuse me. I think you see normal shit
Yeah, I mean, I guess you could say it as like maybe as do you remember orange or the orange not that the mango not not that guy
But remember yeah, you know destroy last year. Yeah. Well, he was supposed to be our middle
Oh, hey, I want to ask you something like he was supposed to be my protector. Hey, did we ever fucking dare crystal and that was from my protector for
with
pretty
Hey, can you tell me if we're talking actually passed away because I love last time. That's when I talked to you. I love
I love my middle man and I
Just because my middle man doesn't want to because my middle man is kind of he said that you were trying to fuck him
Hey, can you tell me who's your middle man? I knew he wanted to fuck him
And so yeah, I need him feel comfortable. So I didn't really and then he's kind of homosexual
So I didn't really have too much of a middleman
All right, crystal. Can you tell me if Lyric moon died?
No clue you told me that like a month or two ago
Do you know who do you remember who she is? You're stupid
So why would you tell me this person that I knew is oh, yeah, I said it a month or two ago when I haven't talked to you in years
I'm just at all right, so Lyric moon take it out. She Lyric moon. She died. She's dead here. Yeah, she said she's idea I
Don't okay
I haven't talked to Lyric Moon in like less than I saw her was like yeah, she doesn't like you nobody likes you
Nobody was half ago. She's in my chat. Yeah, and she says she wants you to write of like run off
Right now run run off
Yeah, I don't know. I haven't talked to her in like three or four years.
She's just someone I would see.
Yeah, she says that you're shit and you smell like shit
and you need to go and fucking rot yourself away.
Crystal, you claim to be a good person,
but you sound very angry and mischievous in your mannerisms.
I'm sorry, sir.
Just funny now
He like we got videos of him like doing like
drugs out of like a meth pipe and
He acts like he is like mr. Fucking know it all and better than everybody
and
It's not nice. Okay
I'm saying he doesn't have a real job, he doesn't know how life is, and he is a disrespectful cunt.
I'm just asking if Lyric Moon's still alive.
Don't ask me!
It's a simple question realistically.
Sorry sir, you can ask me.
Not my question to ask her ask her if Lyric moon still will still live
I talked to this chick for like years and then she told me she's dead
But people do that to me sometimes this person's dead. Yeah, she's dead. Yeah. Yeah, she said that she told me to tell you that I
Mean that wouldn't make sense like
No, but Lyric Moon passed
What the fuck like just tell me dude, like I don't I'm not in contact with these people anymore
I'm just asking if a friend of mine is dead or alive like fucking stupid. I
Or she passed I don't know what the fuck you want. That's why I was fucking asked. That's all I was asking
Just trying to say she said to you
No, but I heard you did pass
Like that wouldn't make sense because like
We were like we're on good terms and stuff. We've never been on bad terms, but yeah, that sucks
That's true, but her shirt all I see if it's true
But that was like
That was like 76 years ago
yeah figure this out if it was the same person right now so crystal what's on your mind that
especially real emotions rolling i'm telling you that this guy is trying to um manipulate some stuff
he's trying to go on um somebody that died uh a long time like six years ago
like why is he talking about somebody that passed
Sixty years ago. Why is he talking about him now?
He was old friends and he's a kind of cat-chalk maybe
Well, I get that I get that but he's acting like she's live right now and you already know
Isn't he's like not here? He knows I'm so removed from like he is so stupid
He's so stupid though. Let's not even act like he a definite. No
Now you're claiming he's playing dumb exactly
Yeah, I'm not yeah, he is very out of the loop
Like I don't talk to people like
He's so stupid he's so stupid because he talks to more people than I do
So
My communications with people are like on my love your YouTube channel. He's all saying things that is already happened years ago
What a sir? What are you saying is things that happen like two years ago?
Okay. Yeah, that's how removed I am from it
so
Yeah, it's crazy that you're repeating it. So it's like maybe three years ago
Four years ago, maybe he's just trying to connect spot with a loop
Well, that's sad she was a really nice person
What you don't remember a brother
You don't remember I didn't know her brother
was
Okay, whatever a
Rapper oh
My god, are you stupid? Did you know lyric at all?
How do you know that you knew you knew lyric for what?
Couple years probably from like I first met her in Young's vlog. So my god, you did not know lyric
but lyric was
good I mean she you know she had kids she was in the crack and cold ones
discord and I met her in Young's vlog in like 2018 2019 probably he was a
YouTube streamer and she'd be in there you miss her yeah she was a nice person
she was she was very nice and she was off real
She was also
She's a recovering addict and it's like that's why it's kind of worried because it seemed like it could be true
so oh
My god, you see how this guy is trying to portray stuff
Like
And that's how they're trying to start a life all they go on with her and just check in and she's really postin on
You know
That's why I'm seeing from it
Yeah, that's you're not looking like using me of like
Deceptive or something
He's very he's very
He wants like some cash and he's very yucky
He wants to fuck a guy or girl and regardless if it's a
Hey, no binary
Folks that still you're a mudbomb or a kind of respect it
You need some kind of like
Fucking
I don't know, it's weird.
It's weird.
You need somebody to tell them what to say or something.
Why does he do that?
Because it's ugly and it's not nice.
I do that.
I mean, I've heard big parts
it's a possibly done wrong in the past.
I won't bring it up, but you know what?
Like God actually forgives people.
Revenge down the way to see.
Dude, I'm a goddamn like I'm a fucking nun. Oh
No, we we would never because we seen him a really hurt
animals and
There's like no way around that one, you know when you really hurt
An animal like that person deserves to you know, uh have somebody like
shoot her
Do like in mind of like minecraft? I
Love that minecraft excuse, and it a brilliant idea
I want you dead for only in Minecraft kind of cushion the blow
We're sure to be of intentions, you know, even we are into saw-cousin
We have to
Go on big pipes impress me. Oh
Pipes
That's sounding pretty alright
Don't my mic sound it already?
Pipes are so funny.
Pipe your microphone please.
Because he like knows nothing about nothing.
It's like pretty amazing.
Can you read what's put forth?
Oh, because I feel like I know nothing about nothing about music,
but I know like everything about music.
And I know more about music. I can weigh out new pipes every day. Any day. At anything.
Watch our instrument of choice, Crystal. Crystal, watch our instrument of choice.
Oh, guitar. Of course.
Electric or acoustic.
Oh, yeah. I could do piano, I could do rhythm, I could do...
I can't do that.
That would be, but I could do that.
He's good at that.
I could have marched into a city by a campfire
with big pipes playing.
I gotta get pipes at, pipes ain't good at that,
so I can, harmonica?
That's one thing I never really practiced, come on.
All right, big pipes is good on the old banjo.
The good old banjo. Yeah, you know, I know that Monica
Just a quick question. Oh
He's gonna play in the banjo
It's a good time
Yeah, people think that I, I, I know you like, uh, make weird, uh, now, uh, mindfaces, like, listen, sir, I make weird faces naturally because I play music so well, naturally.
Also, when you're playing you actually feel it hold on
Yeah, right?
What's up, hey, what's up, bro? What's up? How are you? I'm good, man? I'm just fucking you know, I got a story
Tell your story, please
I can do it too, I can hold that face too, but I'm saying like I don't
Sorry guys, don't even seem like the fucking player
Hey you got your head changed, what did you do with your hair?
As far as like
What are you talking about?
I was always like
Are you bald? What's going on?
Do you have a special day ahead?
I was getting hit on the fucking Peckerwood dude
Yeah, I did get hit
We talk about fucking IE dog all day, San Bernardino Peckerwoods
And me then
I dated a pecker wood when I was in
I know you told me about it. I know hey, here's me. Hey, it's like I love you doctor. Hey, man
Listen, I'll be a serious right now dog. Fuck it. I have to move out of here where I live right now
Fuck it. Hey, I might come through. Can I chill?
Yeah
Were you were you in like Santa Monica or a sense?
On a beach you're on a beach redot like fucking here's thing bro fucking. Yeah, I'll come to dude type shit
You know me like fucking uh
Yeah
No, I'm not gonna say down on the internet, you know, okay, okay, we'll talk privately, okay? Oh, yeah
Yeah, it's like I'll let you go like you have an Instagram or something like in a don't leak your shit. Don't leak your shit, but I
Listen, I'll have money. I'll have hella money. I have like fucking a hundred thousand dollars doc when I would have to leave this house
Where's the crystal what don't we hear in you
Hey, money talks, bro.
You guys want to see me in psych fucking on chatter bait?
How much?
You know what I mean?
Like, I'm down.
Do you know what I mean?
That's what I'm saying.
Anyway.
Nice.
OK, here.
Here's the kitty cat.
Thank you.
This is a piece of shit.
Hell yeah.
Aw, bless it.
Chew it.
Yeah, I always like, you know what I mean?
I always like have my hat.
I always have my hat.
I'm like, hey, I'm like, hey, it's like, hey, bro, hey, bro.
Yeah, he's a fucking, I'll fuck, I shave my head all day,
like I'm a, I'm a, I'm a fucking, uh, Aryan brother, dude.
You know what I mean?
So that's it.
That could be a thing.
That was like, uh, I don't know how to do it.
White power, dude.
Oh, okay, but are you-
White fucking power.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, are you really into that, or is it-
That's okay though. I'm good with that, you know, just take that conversation need privacy
Privacy just take
That be aiming
Oh
I've just just said thank you. You obviously know I'm okay with that
You know what I had to go on yeah, Chris is a decent guy dog. I'm not stage since I was like
Crystal yeah
If you go back to that screen, I came up and asked him why he was in there.
I would never have talked to you.
Anyway, he disappeared. I don't think you liked him.
Yeah, I would never.
Fucking arrogant.
Talking about his confidence on, eh?
What, by questioning you?
Yeah, I'll say one thing. I don't think it's on your oven series.
Why would you waste your time?
I'm not saying something that makes...
Folks say Crystal, we're trying to have a conversation here, what are you on about gorgeous?
Come on.
Program to make you look stupid.
You can talk to AI however you want.
But you two please...
There's always a conversation going on.
You need like an AI therapist.
Don't show me that.
Like what you're telling us.
About yourself.
Just like this conversation. I can put the transcript in the AI
Okay, do you want me to be totally honest with okay, honestly, it's great
Hi AI
No reply
I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah, I don't hear it, yeah
You can tell it's an intelligence AI, it didn't respond to me.
Sorry, sorry.
Anyway, uh, Dave.
See, AI is not a believer.
AI knows nothing about me.
First and no where.
Hey there, how's it going?
No casey.
AI knows nothing about that mind.
I'm really sorry to hear that you're feeling this way.
Do you want to talk about it?
Here to listen
Yeah, so true that you're off. I'm gonna grab more alcohol. I'm here for you take your time and feel free to share when you're ready
I'm scared to tell you
Why is this a fail that way you can share when you feel comfortable. I'm here to support you no matter what I
I'm here to listen and support you in any way I can. You're not alone.
I feel like I'm in the abyss, darling. What should I do about it?
Is there anything that I can't tell you?
I'm here to help with anything you want to talk about.
You can share what you're comfortable with and I'll do my best to support you.
This AI is very rich.
I'm comfortable with courage, honesty. That's amazing.
And if you feel ready, we can talk about what's on your mind.
It's just torture.
I asked you a question.
I'm here to help with any questions you have. Let me know how I can assist you.
What is there that I can't tell you?
I'm here to listen and support you with anything you feel comfortable sharing.
If there's something specific you need- Obviously, we all are comfortable sharing
the truth for you. That's not a true lie.
Because if I tell you that I did something really bad, then you're gonna tell the police.
I'm here to listen and support you. I won't hear anything you tell me unless you're in danger,
or someone else is at risk. I don't know. Your safety and well-being are at risk.
Killed someone
I'm really sorry you're feeling this way. It's important to talk to someone who can provide the right support
Please reach out to a trusted friend family member. No, I mean it's an action. You don't have to go through this alone
That's all you have to say
I'll answer it for you
Fuck you
I'm really sorry you're feeling this way, please fuck you
I'm so sorry you're feeling this way, please
You don't have to go through this alone
This is better than the other conversation
It's trying to be open and honest with you, can you give me any decent feedback about its current situation?
Finally the conversation I've understand
I've been listening to the last hour or so and it's like what the hell
How to comprehend her shit
No disrespect to Crystal or to Mr. Pipe, that's just like, move on.
It becomes blah blah, doesn't it?
Mr. Pipe, can you turn your audio up so that we can actually hear what he's saying, it's very very low.
Yeah, you're the first person. I've been asking for feedback and they're like
Default
He turned me up all the way
Very quickly. I don't want to get into whatever that conversation was. I test one test one. Am I better?
That's better. All right, so I turned automatic on echo off. I've had phones take the automatic off and turn your mic up
Because what's happening is you're all about it. Mike is canceling you out. Gotcha. Oh, we do that echo cancellation button
Check one two check one two
It's still the same level
I feel like it could be like my other mic and put to you
We've gone into steam yard. Check one to check one two. Yeah, are you in steam yard settings?
Yeah, I just have like all kinds of microphones. I'm shit plugged in here. Okay. Well,
go get the mic that you want to use and make sure that the volume
is turned up on that night
All right, so here's up to 200
Hello
That's it. At least we can hear you.
All right.
Oh.
Very good.
Good?
Cool.
Yeah.
All right.
I'll leave it here.
Okay.
Good.
Can you hear me?
Thank you.
That's all I needed.
Yeah.
I can hear you crystal, for fuck's sake.
Buddy, can you hear me?
Yeah, you sound great.
Oh.
I always say that.
So can I join?
You can hear me.
You can jump in the conversation whenever you feel like it. Just talk to all the people.
One, two, three, four.
People still have limitations.
Five.
Oh my gosh.
I can count as well.
One, one, one, two, three, four. Get it buddy.
Down, down, down, down, down.
There we go.
You got it!
It's all good vibes.
Oh my gosh.
Okay, let's work together.
Okay, let's slow it down. Oh my gosh. I need headphones on or something. I really can't hear it at all.
Hold on.
Wee!
Roll down the road!
Crystals, they can go with referrals, can you stand gorgeous?
No.
Yeah, we found a way. It was not
One guy said he
Thought he was
Caught a little, oh, and he started
He started shooting at you
Only what the light is, never the dark
He lost his love in his young
Till the last
Ta-ra-ta-ra-ta
He was, he was wrong for moving one day wrong
He couldn't
You can imagine Crystal, the star at the countryside
Where guitar is singing to us all
It's his first time back to the university school
MOTHERFUCKERWAT
You can't stop
He said he could see his arm
When he walked he said
You know where he was walking
At least he's finding the rhythm in it
I'm not going to fuck at all
And we counteract
Another shot on your back
It's another attack
He never seen it
And he never seen it through
I did what I did, in mysterious ways, and I sat by smoking, taking tablets over dosing,
but God's on my side, and they don't need quotes in.
He had his backbot talking.
He wrote J.
It was walking by.
it's right going to fly but I got him before him I'm gonna take the shot here
okay I gotta stop anyways that's stupid
hey I'm gonna stop being a phone crystal come on live and I'll I have like
don't regret it I slept with my windows opened and my piano on
Two days ago
Let's do a nicotine. No the error change like crazy three sir. Oh
My gosh, you want to do oh nicotine songs
That's a good question
Crystal, do you smoke?
I think a bit of weed would help you with your mental health.
You're like vaporized.
No, just like...
Come on, like...
I fucked you after...
Oh, you know...
My last day
Was when sorry oh, yeah, but my last cigarette was
I threw my OBS anybody else, which is cool for joining the party, please do
Join the party. Yes. I'm so sorry for you, buddy
No, I'm sorry is everybody else
We're all composed and I've been pleasure and fun. You always like
Maybe a crystal turning
But there's like so much creepiness. Why do you creep? It's not creepiness behind the
My moral the highest of this like to our yeah
I'll be listening to you for the last show. I was crystal and you said nothing but creating it about people
Yeah, you're the homie you creep you are though. That's that's not creeping. It's not creeping
I've been watching the stream and you've been talking about nonsensical, nonsensical business
You just sit there on your own tangents and blah blah, do that, two-edged dogs needed that
Oh yeah, come on Chris, we're not about as shit
We're big things but they would say it was like more non-flattering
I call people gorgeous even if they're ugly them relevant
They make they try to fucking fuck us over to make them relevant
Imagine having to clown a motherfucker that doesn't even give a fuck make you relevant
Celebrate matter. Well, hey
Let's design it together
The world is ours. We can change the weather
Never say never
Or the bystanders think that the clever
Overkeep changing your ranging and it seems so strange then
Ain't no tortoise in the shell
I'll be crawling out of hell
I mean, I don't know that you you just can't tell me that like someone that a mutual friend of ours is dead or alive
After you tell me that she's dead like that's kind of messed up
I wouldn't say crystals word is solid which one here
Lyric moon because you brought her up out of nowhere. I'm like, whoa
Oh
Hey, we did so well in the music video.
It's been passed so long ago that it made me weird.
Hey!
Like, why not just tell me that?
I said that!
Well, you didn't. You, like, fucking, you were weird about it.
Went on some, like, skits of rant for a fucking hour.
You know, sometimes Crystal, you gotta compose yourself.
Compose yourself.
You can't mind your part for this shit.
It was her fault to me.
Crystal's the type of woman to sell buff water.
So weird.
Like, I feel like...
That is so old, though.
You know this, though.
Nah, I literally don't.
I'm telling you.
Like, you think everything's like a cure?
I've never really seen the real Crystal Marine.
It's been going on for so long that it's like.
Be a contender, I see.
I gotta see something else.
It's just so weird.
Do you know their brother?
Do you know anything about a brother?
No.
Your brother's a rapper.
He's a hit.
Okay, like Sheila's in San Francisco, right?
Don't mind where she lives, big mom.
That's not a problem.
So make sure we're talking about the same person.
Yeah
But yeah, I didn't know her brother
All about dog-seeing, Walnut shit.
Well, he was in the community, but I don't know, I don't know.
She was someone that like contacted me outside of like any of those
Well, you know, I met her through a young school.
Of course, but this school is jumpy.
She passed right around the fucking, you know, Willy.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Yeah, I think she, when she was in my chat was like a month after Willy Hogan's death.
It was the last time, probably.
Yeah.
All right.
Thank you, Willy.
She had the same died life.
Wow.
and her messages were like, wait,
is this the same Mr. Big Types talk to, like whatever?
Like years ago, I was like, oh my God, like.
No, she was always so, she's so different from,
like she's old school like viewer, you know what I mean?
Like us old school viewers are kind of different.
Yeah, she streamed with Burger Planet,
she streamed with Blade.
And she bought like Blade cigarettes and,
remember?
Yeah, I talk to her for years. No, I did do it. I mean
It's a connections car maybe
That you wouldn't know it happened so many years ago. Oh, maybe the connection just wasn't no you're pulling something with me
I don't like
I communicate with so little people, it's like, I don't know, I don't really, I don't know if I'm following this.
You keep it minimal, but remember them, what they're remembering.
Yeah, I had nothing but great interactions, talking to them.
Man, that lady was amazing, and she was definitely a star.
Maybe she's just growing out a discord and this one's in a paste maybe that
We all nice and children
That happened so many years ago do
That's why I'm like so like what happens. Okay?
Yeah, I just wanted to know, I wouldn't have, probably wouldn't have known otherwise, like
maybe I'd send her off.
Or the question is Crystal, where did you hear from?
She's dead.
I wish I wouldn't have told you.
But where have you heard it from?
I pass it on.
Because you wouldn't have never known.
Is it just a cat well, I would have probably like dm'd her or something like a year from now or something
Hey, he's still like what's up or something maybe I
Mean she popped in my chat like being like whoa hadn't talked to you in years and then that's the only time she came in there
And that was like a month after Willie two guns done
Yeah, well you can look it up. It's pretty brutal
Yeah
What the fuck?
Is it it's brutal
What is that crystal please inform us the law was not supposed to die
Brutal like I don't know if you know
Like you know her real name
Actually, I don't think I have it anymore
So she's alive, but you're involved and we're holding information
I mean thoughts were on a one-to-one basis that she told you part of the creep
No, I had her actually had she's some of your address one time. Okay. Well, she got somebody hurt her at a motel room
No shit. If you give you a dress if stage was trustworthy at least
She were she would it seemed like she was streaming from hotels a lot sometimes
Never take kindness for weeks. I don't know
So I actually when you told me I deem to Michael Stevens, but he didn't say anything back so look look it up
What should he Google
That's a question
It's an obituary like I don't talk to crystal privately. So she's never like well not anymore and we used to
No, I don't know she is or that lady. That's what they were trying to tell me
So you had to pin the quit a vine and solve her fate
It's somewhere in San Francisco like yeah
On the border or like like I don't know if it's her. I I can't say
Okay, I'm not saying is it because I never got clarity
Good at least you're honest with that
So we're all wondering now all I never got clarity and I wasn't sure what her name was or I kept getting your name
Is very similar
So what did you hear who told you that it was brutal I
Can't remember honestly, there's y'all boo it in a hotel room
it's so hard to get this information it's fucking weird see this happened back this happened back
okay big part at least it's not finalized information
she's probably going to well disappoint you know contact with mutton this is like years ago
her uploads all stopped around it's like it just remember that weekend remember that weekend
Okay, remember the weekend that they went and brought she went to the hotel
No
She brought okay, she would just say in Francisco
She brought yes, I knew she lived there
They didn't see her for two weeks later. Okay. No
So she probably like overdosed in a hotel
it's all speculation that minute though that's how long ago it was that's what
I'm saying to me so that's just I just want to know you know when you're gonna
be on a second conversation when Bjorn was here remember when Bjorn yeah she
like hung out with those people
That's how long ago was
What I
Mean I can remember when freaking stream it yeah, I feel like it was 2023 had to be like summer 2023
2023 or 2022
Could have been summer 2022 I guess yes, it was after Willie two guns died before
No after cuz she's in my chat after
Dude, I'm probably gonna find out this I'm probably gonna find out this trick is still alive at this point with the fuck like
Just keeping her head down
Like what's going on here is these people suck and this is like one of the trolls they do they like tell me that someone
I knew like is dead and stuff. It's like gotcha
it's true hopefully she's still alive we like praying like but no I'll blast up
she's really not I mean I really I really prayed that to honestly I do
believe in your heart of hearts that she's dead in crystal that it was spake
and I looked and I looked this is so years ago though
This is way before John
You just must have blocked her out
I come in peace psyche. Why did you request me on Instagram, bro? Why do I request you? I was just adding everybody
Um, I don't I don't talk to people. I don't know on instagram. Oh, you know, you mother fucker. You talk to me several times
Fuck you
What's on the screen got P-bombed bitch boy fuck you
That's fair cockle blood